indusladies.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | Indusladies.com

By visiting and using the [www.IndusLadies.com](http://www.indusladies.com/) website (“IndusLadies”) you acknowledge you have read and agree to be bound by the Privacy Policy contained in this document. If you do not wish to agree to the Privacy Policy, please close this browser session and refrain from using IndusLadies.

IndusLadies is committed to protecting your privacy online. As such, we have adopted and adhere to certain principals concerning the privacy of information you provide to us in the course of using IndusLadies. Please read the following to learn what information we collect from you and how we use that information.

### **1\. Changes to Privacy Policy**

IndusLadies may change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the revised Privacy Policy in the “Privacy Policy” section of the website, located at www.IndusLadies.com/privacy. The revised Privacy Policy is effective immediately when posted on the IndusLadies website. It is your responsibility to review the website and the Privacy Policy periodically to learn of any revisions to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of IndusLadies after the effectiveness of such revisions will constitute your acknowledgment and acceptance of the terms of the revised Privacy Policy.

###   **2\. Protecting Your Privacy**

**IndusLadies is committed to protecting your privacy:**

Your name and contact information will not be shared with anyone for marketing purposes without your permission.

IndusLadies marketing communications are “opt-in,” so you will not receive marketing communications from us unless you choose to receive them. You will, however, receive our monthly newsletter which showcases IndusLadies features.

Your account information is password protected. You are responsible for keeping your password secure and private. Do not share your password with anyone. In the event of any compromise of our website security, IndusLadies will notify you immediately to take action to change your password on the website.

IndusLadies does not knowingly collect any information or allow accounts to be held by users under the age of 13. If an account is discovered by IndusLadies which is believed to be held by a user under 13 years of age, the account and all related postings will be removed by IndusLadies.

###   **3\. What Information We Collect and Store and Why**

**We may collect your email address.**  
We may collect your email address, or other information needed to contact you online. We use it to send you notices related to IndusLadies only. Your email address will never be shared without your permission.

**We may collect other kinds of information from you.**  
When you use IndusLadies, we may collect incidental identifying information about you, such as pages you visit and the amount of time you spend looking at a page. This information does not inherently reveal your identity and will not be linked to you personally. We use this information to improve the functionality of the website. This information may be disclosed only to our staff and to our immediate agents. We may also collect personal information if you provide it in our feedback, comments, or discussion forums.

**We do not collect financial information.**  
IndusLadies does not collect or store your financial information at all.

**All Product Postings and Forum Postings**  
All postings to IndusLadies forums, such as discussions, comments, etc. are stored in our databases and may be archived on-line or off-line in the form of backup tapes or other electronic formats. This information is used to improve the functionality of the website and may be retained even after a posting or your account is “deleted” from the website itself.

###   **4\. Security of Information**

IndusLadies takes security seriously and takes numerous precautions to protect the security of your account information. You can access your account on our website with your username and password. This password is encrypted. We recommend that you do not share your password with anyone. In addition, your account information resides on a secure server that only selected personnel and contractors have access to.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we employ commercially reasonable security measures to protect data, IndusLadies cannot guarantee the security of any information transmitted to or from the website, and is not responsible for the actions of any third parties that may illegally intercept any such information.

###   **5\. Third Party Sites**

This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information IndusLadies collects from you. Other Sites that may be accessible through IndusLadies, through advertising, etc. have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. If you link to any such Site, we urge you review that site’s privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties, including search engines, archive sites or other Third Parties which may gather publicly available information from the IndusLadies website using automated or other methods.

###   **6\. Release of Information**

IndusLadies may release any user information as required by law or in the good faith belief that disclosure of information is reasonably necessary to comply with a subpoena, discovery request, court order or other legal process issued by a court of competent jurisdiction.

IndusLadies may also release any user information in the good faith belief that such disclosure of information is reasonably necessary to enforce the Terms and Conditions of Use for the website, to defend or respond to any legal actions initiated by third-parties related to the user account or content posted by the user; or to protect the personal safety of IndusLadies staff, users, or the general public.

###   **7\. International Users**

By visiting and using the IndusLadies website, you acknowledge that your information may be used and stored on servers located in the United States of America and therefore transferred out of your resident jurisdiction. By using the site, you are consenting to any international exchange of the information provided and you are consenting to the policies contained in this document and posted on the IndusLadies website. You hereby acknowledge that you are providing all information voluntarily, with the understanding that any use of the IndusLadies website is governed by the laws of the United States of America, and you hereby consent to the jurisdiction of the Federal District Court, Western District of Texas regarding any disputes which may arise under this Agreement or use of the website.

###   **8\. Comments and Feedback**

IndusLadies welcomes and encourages your comments and feedback on this Privacy Policy and any of our other website policies. Please visit our feedback center at http://help.indusladies.com/forums/173084-general or email us at [support@IndusLadies.com](mailto:support@IndusLadies.com) with any comments or questions.
